Ooh La La
Britney Spears
压制:随Feng
You don't have to look like a movie star
你没有必要让自己看起来像一个电影明星
Ooh I think you're good just the way you are
我认为最好的你就是最做真实的自己
Tell me if you could would you up and run away with me?
告诉我当你醒来后你可以跟我走
You don't have to roll like a millionaire
你不必看起来像个财大气粗的亿万富翁
Baby I would go with you anywhere
我想和你去任何想去的地方
We don't need no gold, we'll be shining anyway, we'll see
我们不需要披金戴银一样可以闪闪发光 我们会看到
You know can nobody get down like us
你知道没人可以向我们一样疯狂
We don't stop 'till we get enough
我们不会停下来除非嗨到爆
C'mon, turn it up 'till the speakers pop
来吧 把喇叭声音开到最大
Break it down, show me what you've got
不需要循规蹈矩 大胆秀出你自己
my my Ooh baby don't be shy
不要害羞baby
I see that spark flashing in your eye
我看到你眼里闪闪发光的火花
My heart beats fast 'cause I want it all
我的心被小鹿乱撞了因为我想要所有
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
所以baby快点来让我心跳的再加快一点
Take my hand, we can go all night
牵我的手 我们每个晚上都可以一起出去
And spin me round just the way I like
让我天旋地转目眩神迷 OH 我喜欢这样
It feels so good, I don't wanna stop
这种感觉太棒了 我还想要更多
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
baby快点来让我再HIGH 一点
You don't have to wear no designer clothes
你就不要穿不是为你量身定制的衣服
Just as long as we're dancing on the floor
如果我们在地上跳舞
Fingers in my hair and I'm letting go tonight, so free
手指放在我的头发里 只要自由 今晚什么都不管
You know can nobody get down like us
没有人能像我们这样疯狂
We don't stop 'till we get enough
没嗨到爆我们都不会停下来
C'mon, turn it up 'till the speakers pop
来吧 把喇叭的音乐开到最大
Break it down, show me what you've got
然后打破它 秀出你自己
Ooh my my baby don't be shy
OH baby 不要闷骚
I see that spark flashing in your eye
你身体里的欲望都让你眼睛快要燃烧起来了
My heart beats fast 'cause I want it all
而我的心脏已跳到最快了，因为你让我什么都想要
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
快点来让我心跳再快一点
Take my hand, we can go all night
牵我的手，我们每天晚上都出去
And spin me round just the way I like
让我天旋地转目眩神迷，我喜欢这样
It feels so good, I don't wanna stop
感觉太棒了，别停下来
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
让我们再HIGH 一点
Ooh my my baby don't be shy
闷骚男没有好结果
I see that spark flashing in your eye
你眼里的火光闪闪发亮
Ooh my my baby don't be shy
闷骚男没有好结果
I see that spark flashing in your eye
你眼里的火光闪闪发亮
My heart beats fast 'cause I want it all
看，我就敢承认我现在小鹿乱撞，而且什么都想要
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
快点来做我的Ooh la la
Take my hand, we can go all night
牵着我的手，每个晚上我们都可以出去疯狂
And spin me round just the way I like
让我天旋地转，目眩神迷，就像我喜欢的那样
It feels so good, I don't wanna stop
这种感觉太棒了，别停下来
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
快点来和我一起，做我的宝贝
Baby come with me and be my ooh la la
快点来和我一起，做我们想做的事情
压制:随Feng
So baby come with me and be my ooh la la
快点来和我一起，让我看到你最独特的地方